(Leonard:)Sheldon, there's something
I wanna talk to you about before we go.
(Sheldon:)I don't care if anybody gets it,
I'm going as the Doppler effect.
- No, it's not that...
- If I have to, I can demonstrate: Vroom.
(Leonard:)Terrific. Um...
(Leonard:)This party is my first chance for Penny...
(Leonard:)...to see me in the context
of her social group...
(Leonard:)...and I need you not
to embarrass me tonight.
(Sheldon:)What exactly do you mean
by embarrass you?
For example, tonight, no one needs to know
that my middle name is Leakey.
But there's nothing embarrassing
about that.
Your father worked with Louis Leakey,
a great anthropologist.
(Sheldon:)It had nothing to do
with your bed-wetting.
(Leonard:)All I'm saying is that this party
is the perfect opportunity...
(Leonard:)...for Penny to see me
as a member of her peer group...
(Leonard:)...a potential close friend
and perhaps more.